<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>superuser blog</title><link href="http://tyleraland.github.io/blog/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://tyleraland.github.io/blog/feeds/extra.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://tyleraland.github.io/blog/</id><updated>2016-01-01T00:00:00-08:00</updated><entry><title>Privacy Policy</title><link href="http://tyleraland.github.io/blog/privacy-policy.html" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2016-01-01T00:00:00-08:00</updated><author><name>Tyler A Land</name></author><id>tag:tyleraland.github.io,2016-01-01:blog/privacy-policy.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;This site uses Google Analytics to track usage.  Any page that you land on will cause your browser to execute some javascript code, informing Google's servers that you have visited this site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What kinds of data does Google Analytics record?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The duration of your stay, which browser you're using, the previous web page that linked you here, and potentially quite a bit more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, and notably, I have enabled Remarketing with Google Analytics.  This allows Google to track additional information about you such as your estimated age, estimated gender, and categories of interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What do I do with your data?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tracking information allows me to better understand who is coming to my site and what content they're reading.  With this information, I can make more informed decisions when producing content.  I may summarize and publicly share aggregate statistics of the data that I collect.  No personally identifying information is included in this reporting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also want to be better informed about how Google Analytics works and what it is capable of.  All of my activity falls within the bounds of the &lt;a href="http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html"&gt;Google Analytics Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Why am I telling you this?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Google requires that users of Google Analytics provide a privacy policy on their site which is easily accessible that includes specific information describing how it is being used to track.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Want to opt out?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, you are more than willing to &lt;a href="https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/"&gt;opt out of Google Analytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>